bossgoo.com 2017-06-06

# China Suppliers & Manufacturers, China wholesale Products Directory - Bossgoo.com - Privacy HelpCenter

Privacy Policy

Bossgoo.com makes a firm commitment to protect your privacy. The following policy, as part of Terms & Conditions which has to be agreed with by users while visiting our website, provides details of how your information is treated. This policy may be subject to changes without notice. So please check the latest version periodically.

Our Commitment to Privacy

Bossgoo respects the privacy of your information. Our Privacy Policy governs our online information practices and reflects our commitment to protect your privacy.

Which information will be collected by Bossgoo?

Account Data  
We collect all the information in your account on Bossgoo.com, such as your company name, address, contact person, telephone number, fax number, email and etc. This is to enforce the agreement between you and Bossgoo.com, make you reachable by those potential trade partners, or troubleshoot problems.

Hidden Data  
In addition to the account data, we also collect the information from the record of your visiting history on our website, including but not limited to, cookies, IP address, and so on. The information is not used to identify you, but the necessary methods to avoid being attacked by hackers, and for the purpose of making customized content service to users. Additionally, through processing comprehensive statistic analysis, we are endeavoring to provide you with more and more efficient functions to facilitate our service. To visit Bossgoo.com, your browser has to be configured to accept cookies.

Other Information  
Sometimes we may contract with third parties to offer you the products or services which we ourselves do not offer. To fully access and use such service, you may be asked to provide certain information.

How would Bossgoo treat those information?

The information, such as company name, address, contact person, telephone number, etc. will be posted on Bossgoo.com publicly, and accessible to all the users. Thus, you'd better exercise caution when deciding to release any information that is identifiable to you.

Based on the above information, Bossgoo.com conducts analysis and research, regarding users' distribution of industry, geographic location, and so on. It is for better understanding of our users, and is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis.Bossgoo.com maintains the right to share the analytic results with business partners.

Security Measures

Your account information and profile are password protected. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. Remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

Cookies

Bossgoo may set and access cookies on your computer.

Bossgoo allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Bossgoo's cookies.

Bossgoo uses web beacons to access our cookies within and outside our network of web sites and in connection with Bossgoo products and services.

Disclosure of Information

Bossgoo reserve the right to disclose your Collected Information to relevant authorities where we have reason to believe that such disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be infringing or threatening to infringe, or who may otherwise be causing injury to or interference with, the title, rights, interests or property of bossgoo.com, our Users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.

We also reserve the right to disclose Collected Information in response to a subpoena or other judicial order or when we reasonably believe that such disclosure is required by law, regulation or administrative order of any court, governmental or regulatory authority.

If we have reason to believe that a User is in breach of the Terms of User Agreement or any other agreement with us, then we reserve the right to make public or otherwise disclose such User's Collected Information in order to pursue our claim or prevent further injury to bossgoo or others.

Changes to Privacy Policy

Bossgoo.com may amend this policy from time to time.Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be communicated through our posting an amended and restated Privacy Policy on our Site. Our posting the amended and restated Privacy Policy will make such new Privacy Policy immediately effective. You agree that all Collected Information (whether or not collected prior to or after the new policy became effective) will be governed by the newest Privacy Policy then in effect. If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact Bossgoo.com and specifically request that Bossgoo.com return and/or destroy all copies of all or part of your Collected Information Bossgoo.com's possession. This Privacy Policy was last amended on Jan 1, 2008.

Your feedback or Contact us

Should you have any suggestion on our Privacy Policy, please contact us ,Bossgoo welcomes your continuous input regarding our Privacy Policy or our services provided to you. You may send us your comments and responses to [service@bossgoo.com](mailto:service@bossgoo.com)
